There's a fire starting in my
heart,
Reaching a fever pitch and it's
bringing me out the dark.
Finally, I can see you crystal
clear,
Go ahead and sell me out and
I'll lay your ship bare,
See how I'll leave with every
piece of you,
Don't underestimate the things
that I will do.
There's a fire starting in my
heart,
Reaching a fever pitch and it's
bring me out the dark.
The scars of your love remind me
of us,
They keep me thinking that we
almost had it all.
The scars of your love, they
leave me breathless,
I can't help feeling,
We could have had it all, (Your
gonna wish you, never had met
me)
Rolling in the deep, (Tears are
gonna fall, rolling in the deep)
You had my heart inside your
hand, (You're gonna wish you
never had met me)
And you played it to the beat.
(Tears are gonna fall, rolling
in the deep)
Baby, I have no story to be
told,
But I've heard one on you and
I'm gonna make your head burn,
Think of me in the depths of
your despair,
Making a home down there as mine
sure won't be shared,
The scars of your love remind me
of us, (You're gonna wish you
never had met me)
They keep me thinking that we
almost had it all. (Tears are
gonna fall, rolling in the deep)
The scars of your love, they
leave me breathless, (You're
gonna wish you never had met me)
I can't help feeling, (Tears are
gonna fall, rolling in the deep)
We could have had it all,
(You're gonna wish you never had
met me)
Rolling in the deep. (Tears are
gonna fall, rolling in the deep)
You had my heart inside your
hand, (You're gonna wish you
never had met me)
And you played it to the beat.
(Tears are gonna fall, rolling
in the deep)
Could have had it all,
Rolling in the deep,
You had my heart inside of your
hands,
But you played it with a
beating.
Throw your soul through every
open door,
Count your blessings to find
what you look for.
Turn my sorrow into treasured
gold,
You'll pay me back in kind and
reap just what you've sown.
(You're gonna wish you never had
met me) We could have had it
all,
(Tears are gonna fall, rolling
in the deep) We could have had
it all.
(You're gonna wish you never had
met me), It all, it all, it all.
(Tears are gonna fall, rolling
in the deep)
We could have had it all,
(You're gonna wish you never had
met me)
Rolling in the deep. (Tears are
gonna fall, rolling in the deep
You had my heart inside of your
hand, (You're gonna wish you
never had met me)
And you played it to the beat.
(Tears are gonna fall, rolling
in the deep)
Could have had it all, (You're
gonna wish you never had met me)
Rolling in the deep. (Tears are
gonna fall, rolling in the deep)
You had my heart inside of your
hands, (You're gonna wish you
never had met me
But you played it,
You played it,
You played it to the beat.
www.RentAnAdviser.com