by RentAnAdviser.com
Oh
Oh, her eyes, her eyes make the stars
look like they're not shinin'
Her hair, her hair falls perfectly
without her tryin'
She's so beautiful, uh
And I tell her every day
Yeah, I know, I know, when I compliment
her, she won't believe me
And it's so, it's so sad to think
that she don't see what I see
But every time she asks
me, "Do I look okay?"
I say
When I see your face
There's not a thing that
I would change
'Cause you're amazing
Just the way you are
And when you smile
The whole world stops and
stares for a while
'Cause, girl, you're amazing
Just the way you are
Yeah
Her lips, her lips, I could kiss
them all day if she'd let me
Her laugh, her laugh, she hates,
but I think it's so sexy
She's so beautiful, uh
And I tell her every day
Oh, you know, you know, you know
I'd never ask you to change
If perfect's what you're searching
for, then just stay the same
So don't even bother askin'
if you look okay
You know I'll say
When I see your face
There's not a thing that
I would change
'Cause you're amazing
Just the way you are
And when you smile
The whole world stops and
stares for a while
'Cause, girl, you're amazing
Just the way you are
The way you are
Girl, you're amazing
Just the way you are
When I see your face
There's not a thing that
I would change
'Cause you're amazing
Just the way you are
And when you smile
The whole world stops and
stares for a while
'Cause, girl, you're amazing
Just the way you are
Yeah
by RentAnAdviser.com