by RentAnAdviser.com
When you try your best,
but you don't succeed
When you get what you want,
but not what you need
When you feel so tired,
but you can't sleep
Stuck in reverse
And the tears come streaming
down your face
When you lose something
you can't replace
When you love someone,
but it goes to waste
Could it be worse?
Lights will guide you home
And ignite your bones
And I will try to fix you
And high up above or down below
When you're too in love to let it go
But if you never try,
you'll never know
Just what you're worth
Lights will guide you home
And ignite your bones
And I will try to fix you
Tears stream down your face
When you lose something
you cannot replace
Tears stream down your face, and I
Tears stream down your face
I promise you I will learn
from my mistakes
Tears stream down your face, and I
Lights will guide you home
And ignite your bones
And I will try to fix you
by RentAnAdviser.com