by RentAnAdviser.com ©
One. one. one...
Talkin in my sleep at night
Makin' myselfcrazy
(Out of my mind. out of my mind)
Wrote it down and read it out
Hopin' it would save me
(Too many times. too many times)
My love. he makes me feel
like nobody else
Nobody else
But my love. he doesn't love
me. so I tell myself
I tell myself
One. don't pick upthe phone
You know he's only calling cause
he's drunk and alone
Two. don't let him in
You'll haveto kick him out again
Three. don't be his friend
You know you're gonna wake up
in his bed in the morning
And if you're under him. you
ain't getting over him
I got new ru les. I count em
I got new rules. I count em
I gotta tell them to myself
I keep pushin' forwards. but he
keeps pullin' me backwards
(Nowhere to tum) no way
(Nowhere to turn) no
Now l'm standing back from it.
I finally see the pattern
(I never learn. I never leam)
But my love. he doesn't love
me. so I tell myself
I tell myself
I do. I do. I do
One. don't pick upthe phone
You know he's only calling cause
he's drunk and alone
Two. don't let him in
You'll haveto kick him out again
Three. don't be his friend
You knowyou're gonna wake up
in his bed in the morning
And if youre under him. you
ain't getting over him
I got new ru les. I count em
I got new rules. I count em
I gotta tell them to myself
Practice makes perfect
l'm still tryna' learn it by heart
(I got new rules. I count em)
Eat. sleep. and breathe it
Rehearse and repeat it. 'cause I
(I got new. I got new. I...)
One. don't pick upthe phone
You know he's only calling 'cause
he's drunk and alone
Two. don't let him in
You'll have to kick him out again
Three, don't be his friend
You know you're gonna wake up
in his bed in the morning
And if you're under him. you
ain't getting over him
I got new ru les. I count 'em
I got new rules. I count 'em
I gotta tell them to myself
Don't let him in. don't let him in
Don't, don't, don't, don't
Don't be his friend,
don't be his friend
Don't. don't. don't. don't
Don't let him in. don't let him in
Don't be his friend.
don't be his friend
Don't. don't. don't. don't
You gettin' over him
by RentAnAdviser.com ©