Is this the real life?
Is this just fantasy?
Caught in a landslide
No escape from reality
Open your eyes
Look up to the skies and see
I'm just a poor boy, I need no sympathy
Because I'm easy come, easy go
A little high, little low
Anyway the wind blows, doesn't
really matter to me, to me
Mama, just killed a man
Put a gun against his head
Pulled my trigger, now he's dead
Mama, life had just begun
But now I've gone and thrown it all away
Mama, ooo
Didn't mean to make you cry
If I'm not back again this time tomorrow
Carry on, carry on, as if
nothing really matters
Too late, my time has come
Sends shivers down my spine
Body's aching all the time
Goodbye everybody I've got to go
Gotta leave you all behind and
face the truth
Mama, ooo (anyway the wind blows)
I don't want to die
I sometimes wish I'd never
been born at all
I see a little silhouetto of a man
Scaramouch, scaramouch will
you do the fandango
Thunderbolt and lightning very
very frightening me
Gallileo, Gallileo,
Gallileo Figaro - magnifico
But I'm just a poor boy and
nobody loves me
He's just a poor boy from a poor family
Spare him his life from this monstrosity
Easy come easy go will you let me go
Bismillah! No we will not let
you go - let him go
Bismillah! We will not let you
go - let him go
go let me go
Will not let you go let me go (never)
Never let you go let me go
Never let me go ooo
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh mama mia, mama mia, mama
mia let me go
Beelzebub has a devil put aside for me
For me
So you think you can stop me
and spit in my eye
So you think you can love me
and leave me to die
Oh baby can't do this to me baby
Just gotta get out just gotta
get right outta here
Ooh yeah, ooh yeah
Nothing really matters
Anyone can see
Nothing really matters nothing
really matters to me
Anyway the wind blows
www.RentAnAdviser.com